♫ Magic stack of old cards ♫
♫ From the Fortune Teller, ♫
♫ Eight clones summoned to this world, ♫
♫ And every one of them: ♫
♫ A different look, ♫
♫ A different hook, ♫
♫ And different outlook ♫
♫ On what’s good ♫
♫ And who’s the king, and who’s the jack, ♫
♫ Wish you good luck on keeping track! ♫
♫ What could possibly go wrong? ♫
♫  EVERYTHING WENT WRONG! ♫
Whatcha waaatchin’?
Time to...
ROCK AND ROLL!!
No! We’re not watching this crap today!
But it’s my turn today!
Waru! We never took turns!
Give it...
Oh, Spade. Give it to me!
You never watch TV anyway.
I am tonight!
They’re showing the 16th century Ottoman-Hungarian War on “Epoch-TV”.
Oh, turn it up!
Ugh, not more power struggles!
We watch TV to become stupider, not smarter!
Are there concubines in this?
Spade, don’t give him the remote!
Or he’ll put on his soap operas for housewives!
They’re not just for housewives,
but also for divorced men in their 30s!
Uh… what about a cooking show?
Keep your calm, Fёdor…
…You can watch it later!
NO, YOU!!!
My favourite cartoons are on today! Gimme!
NOOOOOO!
Phew!
Whoops!
AH! WARU?!
Who cares, it’s just comics.
Bah! You’ll make more!
More?
MORE?!
JUST CO-…
Why do I bother?..
Hm!
You think making comics is easy?
Is it not?
If we consult history,
the predecessors of comic books, such as medieval illustrations,
were a primitive form of entertainment…
for the peasants.
Need I remind you,
that I’m here to get stupider!
I just wanted to watch some cartoons…
Exactly! D’ya hear what our Spongy friend said?
Cartoons are cool, comics are SHI-…
So, you’re saying YOU’LL do better than me?
We’re literally your clones. You’ve literally called us up for this stuff.
Weeell, if it’s that easy…
…then all of you will make a comic each.
The best one, in my…
Ahem!
opinion!
…will choose what we’re gonna watch.
(laughs)
Pffft, who needs a remote!
Good luck!
Phew! Well, that’ll keep them busy till the evening...
I want this one! And this one!
OHHH, THIS ONE’S PRETTY!
.
..
...
Where’s all the paper?
You can have toilet paper.
WARU!
I’ve thought up a masterpiece!
And for that I need A LOT of paper!
You’re not gonna need THESE anymore.
Aha! I’ll do something much much better!
Hmm…
Hmm… Comic books, comic books… What kinds are there?
There’s some about safety, like in school!
No! Too boring!
Or maybe caricatures, like in the Punch magazine?...
No! Too vulgar!
Memes?
Agh, still no!
Yes! I’ll have the best graphic novel!
If I could learn how to draw…
I can’t decide… What if Fёdor doesn’t like it?
Edits!
That’s such a huge responsibility!
I need a partner.
Hmm, it’s important to break the work into stages.
For starters...
I must collect more data.
This is still  not enough!
Um, like this? Do you like it?
Hm...
yeah!.. It’s fine.
Is something wrong? Should I fix anything?
Mmm… give me that pencil.
Okay, I see. Can I get back to work?
Romeo?
(giggles)
(groaning in disgust)
ОH!
(evil laugh)
Are you sleeping in Fёdor’s bed?
Are you stealing someone else’s art?
(evil laugh)
I received power that our father never dreamed of!
He was never your father!
NANI?!
…And then their swords cross!
So, how’s it going?
Oh! This is great. Just how I imagined it.
Oh, don’t mention it, I’m not…
— I’m home!
THE DEADLINE! QUICK!
Lookie who I found.
Who IS that?
Gabriel! It’s been a while!
Where was he?
Uhhhh…
Gabriel!
Gabri! Gabri-Gabri-Gabri!
You’re just in time!
Did you finish the comic?
Better than that! Look.
Um… What… is that?
I. Made. An animation!
Why is it only three frames?
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT IS TO MAKE CARTOONS?!
Alright, alright, alright…
Move over! King in the castle!
Oh wow! This is beautiful.
Did you copy the first result for “manga” on Google?
WHAT?! No!
The second?
…Yeah.
Ahem! Who’s next?
Woah…
I think I’ll restrict your Internet access…
That’s enough! It’s our turn.
Get ready to read the most exciting saga about a fearless knight,
whose heroic exploits are glorified by mankin-…
It’s kinda generic.
What?..
I mean, it’s corny. It doesn’t hook you in.
The characters’ motivation is unfounded!
But, overall, it’s good.
Especially compared to everyone else’s comics…
AHH! Oh, I’ve been looking for that!
Kuromaku, are you taking part?
Yes, I’ve just finished it.
Ah, so that’s your way of making comics... I thought you were writing a whole novel.
Using statistical analysis, I have calculated the formula for the perfect comic.
Mmm, impressive. And… what are the results?
I have found…
Nothing.
Now I know.
I’m proud of you, guys.
I thought you’d give up on the idea, or turn the place upside down again.
But you all actually did great.
And so, the rightful winner is the comic by Spade, and…
can I take part?
I think we have a winner!..
What the?...
WOAH!
It’s amazing!
What a story! And all on one page!
Is this loss?
IT’S BEAUTIFUL!
We have to show it to the world!
WA-…
(off-screen laughter)
Ouch! Dang, Charlie! Watch where you’re throwin’!
Oh, sorry! I don’t even know how I did that!
How long do we have to watch this for?
The whole season…
(Waru sighs)
(Gabriel giggles triumphantly.)
AAA!
Good sleep is the key to…
JUST LEAVE!